[Music]
and now a career retrospective with
Jason seagull and Cameron Diaz Cameron
Diaz made film history with her
breathtaking performance in a movie
known in many circles as gang bangs of
New York thank you Jason but what about
your triumphant Tri XX Blockbuster how I
wet your mother magnificent and not a
dry eye or seat in the house you're kind
two words Charlie's anal one and two
Bravo oh thank you and you and fingering
Sarah Marshall you in night and lay you
in five rear engagement you in the
holiday Jeff who lives to Bone there's
something in Mary Freaks and cheeks
Vanella thighs galver straddle the green
horny knocked up the box then we came
together yeah we did in sex tape enjoyed
your video hi and welcome oh crap you
actually sent it to all our friends and
family technically yes what do you think
the adult title for sex tape will end up
being sex
tape